Our Chivalry Code. GDPR & privacy.  
On all our linking adventures and spelling quests we expect everyone to act in a courteous and respectful way. We have our own code of chivalry and respect all our users, students, pupils, teachers, et al.  
Our legal information below goes into more detail, but be in no doubt we use cookies and gather additional information only in so far as to better be in your service fair squires and maidens.

Sir Linkalot’s WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY  
Privacy Policy  
Sir Linkalot is committed to safeguarding your privacy. We have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. Contact us at if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.  
By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy refers to our website. For app details please see links ‘in-app’ via the menu.  
Sections  
1\. Definitions used in this Policy  
2\. Data protection principles we follow  
3\. What rights do you have regarding your Personal Data  
4\. What Personal Data we gather about you  
5\. How we use your Personal Data  
6\. Who else has access to your Personal Data  
7\. How we secure your data  
8\. Information about cookies  
9\. Contact information  
Definitions  
Personal Data – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. Processing – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data. Data subject – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed. Child – a natural person under 16 years of age. We/us (either capitalized or not) –  
Data Protection Principles  
We promise to follow the following data protection principles:  
• Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.  
• Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.  
• Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.  
• Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.  
• We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.  
• We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.  
Data Subject’s rights  
The Data Subject has the following rights:  
1\. Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.  
2\. Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.  
3\. Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.  
4\. Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.  
5\. Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.  
6\. Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.  
7\. Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.  
8\. Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.  
9\. Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us: https://sirlinkalot.org/contact.  
10\. Right for the help of a supervisory authority – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.  
11\. Right to withdraw consent – you have the right to withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.  
Data we gather  
Information you have provided us with This might be your e-mail address, name and billing address – mainly information that is necessary for delivering you our product and service offering, or to enhance your customer experience with us. We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.  
Information automatically collected about you This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your browsing history, your IP address, your order history (if there is any). This information is used to improve your customer experience. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.  
Information from our partners We gather information from our trusted partners only when necessary, with confirmation that they have legal grounds to share that information with us. This is either information you have provided them directly with or that they have gathered about you on other legal grounds. Information that you provide via App Store is kept according to the Privacy Policy of that organisation.  
Publicly available information We might gather information about you that is publicly available (for example, from a company website or marketing materials).  
How we use your Personal Data We do not rent or sell your Personal Information to anyone, and endeavour to gather the minimum amount of data from you to improve our activities, and/or provide you with our products and services.  
We use your Personal Data in order to:  
• provide our service to you. This includes, for example, providing you with our products and services that you have requested; providing you with promotional items at your request and communicating with you in relation to those products and services; communicating and interacting with you; and notifying you of changes to any services.  
• enhance your customer experience;  
• fulfil an obligation under law or contract.  
We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent.  
On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:  
• to identify you;  
• to provide you a service or to send/offer you a product;  
• to communicate either for sales or invoicing.  
On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:  
• to send you tailored offers (from us);  
• to administer and analyse our customer base (purchasing behaviour and history) in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of products/services offered and/or provided;  
• to conduct questionnaires concerning customer satisfaction.  
As long as you have not informed us otherwise, we consider offering you products/services that are similar or same to your purchasing history/browsing behaviour to be our legitimate interest.  
With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:  
• to send you newsletters and campaign offers (from);  
• for other purposes we have explicitly asked and gathered your consent for.  
We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfil obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised. We save your billing information and other information gathered about you for as long as needed for accounting purposes or other obligations deriving from law.  
We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:  
• the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;  
• the further Processing would not harm your interests and;  
• there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.  
We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.  
Who else can access your Personal Data We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience. We share your data with:  
For marketing and website performance purposes:  
• Mailerlite  
• Google Analytics  
• Social network code to provide you with video and sharing data, inc. Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, Vimeo.  
We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it. We comply with data protection requirements by using services that have implemented the Privacy Shield framework for EU citizen’s data.  
Marketing Communications You can opt-out of receiving certain promotional or marketing communications from us at any time, by using the unsubscribe link in the emails communications we send, or by contacting us.  
If you have any account for our Services, we will still send you non-promotional communications, like service-related emails.  
Exercising Data Subject Rights If you would like to access, review, update, rectify, and delete any Personal Information we hold about you, or exercise any other data subject right available to you under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you can request it from us and we will respond to you as in a timely manner.  
Please note that we may still use any aggregated and de-identified Personal Information that does not identify any individual, and may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  
How we secure your data We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and utilise software solutions to mitigate against security threats.  
Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.  
If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.  
Children We collect minimal but necessary information from children as this is the core audience for our product. We never share this information, and all marketing (such as via email list or social posts) is suitable for this audience.  
Cookies and other technologies we use We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.  
A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.  
We use cookies for the following purposes:  
• Necessary cookies – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.  
• Functionality cookies – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalised features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.  
• Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services  
• Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.  
You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as optout.aboutads.info or youronlinechoices.com. For more information about cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org.  
We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review here. If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the Google Analytics opt-out page.  
Linked Websites For your convenience, hyperlinks may be posted on our Websites that link to other websites (the “Linked Sites”). We are not responsible for, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, the privacy practices of any Linked Sites or of any companies that we do not own or control. Linked Sites may collect information in addition to that which we collect on the Websites. We do not endorse any of these Linked Sites, the services or products described or offered on such Linked Sites, or any of the content contained on the Linked Sites. We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of each Linked Site that you visit to understand how the information that is collected about you is used and protected.  
Contact Information The Supervisory Authority in the UK is ico. — The Information Commissioner’s Office. They can be found at: https://ico.org.uk/ and contacted on 0303 123 1113 or (44) 1625 545 700. They can provide more information about your rights regarding personal data, and the responsibility of companies using this data.  
Privacy Policy Changes We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the privacy policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this privacy policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this privacy policy, without your prior consent.  
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.  
We endeavour to improve and update our GDPR compliance and privacy protections for our customers and website visitors on an ongoing basis.  
Contact If you have any questions regarding this policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us here: https://sirlinkalot.org/contact.

###### Get in touch

###### Thinkalink Digital Ltd

* Hurstwood Cottages
* Haywards Heath
* RH17 7QZ
* United Kingdom
* Company Registration: 11231287

© Sir Linkalot 2021. All rights reserved.
